<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Human in the Loop</title>
    <description>AI agents, GenAI innovation, curated tools and career advice for an AI-first world</description>
    <link>https://humanintheloop.beehiiv.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 09:01:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>♾️ Welcome to Human in the Loop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Thanks for joining Human in the Loop. I'm Andreas — and I'm genuinely excited you're here.</p>
        
        <p><strong>Let's get straight to it. I'm here to do 3 things for you:</strong></p>
        <ol>
          <li>Make sense of AI agents and current GenAI innovation</li>
          <li>Drop curated tools and real-world use cases</li>
          <li>Tactical career advice so you can grow fast in an AI-first world</li>
        </ol>
        
        <h2>Why I started this</h2>
        
        <p>Everyone has an opinion on AI. Some say it's overhyped. Others call it the fourth industrial revolution. I'm not here for the noise — I'm here for the response.</p>
        
        <p>Because whether you're an optimist or a skeptic, the tech is already here — reshaping how we live, work, and make decisions.</p>
        
        <p>In this moment, you can either be the <strong>driver</strong> — or the <strong>passenger</strong>. Drivers set the direction. Passengers follow. And right now, while the tools are still early and the rules are still forming, you have a rare chance to lead. Those who choose to engage now — who experiment, iterate, and learn — will shape what comes next.</p>
        
        <p>That's why I created Human in the Loop — to make sure you're the driver.</p>
        
        <h3>IMPORTANT — Next steps</h3>
        <ol>
          <li>Reply to this email with a quick "Yes".</li>
          <li>Move this e-mail to your Primary inbox</li>
        </ol>
        
        <p><strong>Welcome to the loop and excited to have you here.</strong></p>
        
        <p>See you soon!</p>
        
        <p>— Andreas</p>
        
        <p><strong>P.S. I read every reply — if there's something you want me to cover or share your thoughts on, just let me know!</strong></p>
      ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Andreas (Human in the Loop)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">humanintheloop-welcome-2025-01-23</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>